Hi Friends, hope you all are doing good.
Today, In this video, I will give you details,
regarding max bupa's health Companion plan, and later in this video,
I will also talk about special features and benefits of this plan
I have made this video on demand of viewers.
This video is going to be very beneficial for you,
so guys please watch this video till the end, beacuse in the end,
I am going to answer few questions which my viewers
generally use to ask me in the comments or on whatsapp
So, before starting the video, I would like to thank all my viewers,
who keep supporting us and who liked our videos and
those who have already subscribed to my channel
And if you have not yet subscribed to my channel then please
click on subscribe, like my video and press the bell icon
This will help you to stay updated with my latest videos
And if you are watching my video first time,
then welcome to my Channel, I am your health consultant kajal
Lets Start. Friends max bupa has bring, health companion plan for you,
which is a thoughtful plan for thoughtful people,
it is a value for money plan
Apart from it, this plan provide you some unique features also,
And the best thing about this plan is,
that, this plan provides you the benefits of an
Accidental emergency cover from Day 1.
Hope you guys already know that, our health can affect us
any time due to many factors,
like pollution adulteration and healthy lifestyle
and our some addictive habits,
this is why this plan covers accidental medical emergency
without any waiting period
It also provides you the facility of pre and post hospitalization.
It means before you get hospitalized there are few expenses
which you get in your pre medical home treatment
this plan also covers those expenses upto 30 days.
Apart from this when you get discharge from hospital
and go back to your home,
then you also get some expenses regarding
your post medical treatment
at your home, expenses like medicines of patient doctors fees
and diagnostic test etc.
This plan also covers these expenses upto 60 days.
Now comes the inpatient hospitalization, which covers room charges,
ICU charges operation charges and oxygen blood anaesthesia,
you get all these charges covered in this plan up to sum insured.
All day care treatment facility is available in this plan,
all day care treatments means those treatments
which are done in less than 24 hours
In such treatments patient is not required to get admitted
in the hospital
Max Bupa Health Companion plan cover all such day care treatment like
chemotherapy, radiotherapy, laser operations etc up to sum insured
Organ donor is also covered up to sum insured in this plan
Emergency ground ambulance is covered upto Rs 3000/- per event
Domiciliary treatment facility is also available in this plan. Domiciliary
treatment means, in case patient did not get admitted in the hospital
due to non availability of rooms in hospital.
In this situation you can get your treatment done in your home
and expenses regarding your home medical treatment are
covered in this plan upto sum insured
Animal bite covered is available to you upto rupees 7500
Alternative treatment facility is also covered in this plan. In case you
want to take non allopathic treatments like unani, siddha and ayurveda
all these kinds of treatments are  available upto sum insured
Friends it was all about unique features of this plan
Now I will tell you what are the unique benefits of this plan
First comes the no claim bonus. In Max Bupa Health companion plan
you get 20% bonus in case you do not take any claim
and it will go upto maximum up 100%
Guys you all know, that day by day medical expenses are touching skies
and in coming years
we have no idea that how higher our hospital bills will go
this is why Max Bupa provided you claim free bonus every year
and the best thing about this is your bonus will never get
reduced in case of claim
and you don't have to pay extra premium for this
Another benefit of complementary  health checkup is provided to you
which is completely free of cost
and you will get this benefit every year in this plan on
renewal of your policy
Refill benefit is also available incase your sum insured will get
exhausted at the time of your claim
Company will provide you with the refill amount
which is equal to the amount of your base sum insured
and other members of your family can use this amount for any illness
Now guys do you know that room rent is a basic component in the
policy, but still few companies set limits on room rent
which directly affects customers pocket and apart from this
few companies also put co-payment clause in their policies
because of which customers need to pay part of treatment from
their pocket, but in Max Bupa health companion plan
there is no kind of capping in room rents
Single private room is available to you of any category
there is no co-payments at any age in this policy
Hospital cash upto Rs.4000/- is available in this plan
You get the facility of lifelong renewal in this plan
You can take some insured starting from 3 lakh to 1 crore in this plan
Child age is defined as 91 days to 21 years
In this plan for adults minimum age is 18 years
and maximum age is not define
Let's talk about the waiting period of this plan,
you get initial waiting period of 30 days
and this is not applicable on accidental injuries
For pre existing disease you get the waiting period of 3 to 4 years
and for specific disease it is 2 years